https://mortgagemint.com/privacy/

PRIVACY - MortgageMint® Official Site - Colorado Mortgage Lender
Chat with us,
powered by LiveChat
live chat software
303-333-6468 Open 7 Days a Week - Call Today!
PRIVACY POLICY
The Mortgage Mint®,LLC recognizes and respects the importance of maintaining the privacy of our customers and has established a privacy policy as a result.
Why do we gather information?
We only gather information necessary to better your visit to MortgageMint.com.
Specifically we gather information to:
Better understand your needs
Better serve your requests
Keep accurate records of your preferences and requests
The Mortgage Mint®,LLC. does not believe in selling mailing lists or any other mass marketing techniques. Your private information will remain private at all times. The Mortgage Mint®,LLC. is a Colorado Mortgage Lender, Colorado Mortgage Company.
Security Information:
The Mortgage Mint®,LLC understands that financial information is a sensitive subject with our past, current and future clients. With your safety in mind, we have done everything possible to protect your private information.
This site encrypts your information prior to transmission over the Internet using secure socket layer (SSL) encryption technology.
FACTS : What Does The MortgageMint LLC do with your Personal Information?
WHY?  Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also required us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.
WHAT?  The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This information can include:
Social Security Number and Income
Payment history and credit history
Assets and credit scores
When you are NO LONGER our customer, we continue to share your information as described in this notice.
HOW?  All financial companies need to share customers’ personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their customers’ personal information; the reasons THE  MORTGAGEMINT, LLC chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.
Reasons we can share your personal information:
For our everyday business purposes — We do not share
— such as to process your transactions, maintain
your account(s), responds to court orders and legal
investigations, or report to credit bureaus
Can you limit this sharing?—–We do not share
For our marketing purposes — We do not share
— to offer our products and services to you
Can you limit this sharing?—–We do not share
For joint marketing with other financial companies – We do not share
Can you limit this sharing?—–We do not share
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes — We do not share
— information about your transactions
Can you limit this sharing?—–We do not share
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes — We do not share
— information about your creditworthiness
Can you limit this sharing?—–We do not share
For our affiliates to market to you — We do not share
Can you limit this sharing?—–We do not share
For non-affiliates to market to you –We do not share
Can you limit this sharing?—–We do not share
QUESTIONS?
Who we are…Who is providing the notice?
THE MORTAGEMINT, LLC
What we do….How does the MORTGAGEMINT, LLC protect my information?
To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law.  These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.
How does THE MORTGAGEMINT, LLC collect my personal information?
We collect your personal information, for example, when you
apply for a loan or give us your income information
provide employment information or tell us about your investments or retirement portfolio
show your drivers license
Why can’t I limit all sharing?
Federal law give you the right to limit only:
Sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes – information about your creditworthiness
affiliates from using your information to market to you
sharing for non-affiliates to market to you
State Laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing.
DEFINITIONS?
Affiliates: Companies related by common ownership or control.  They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.
Non-affiliates: Companies not related by common ownership or control.  They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.
Joint Marketing:  A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you.
REGULATED BY THE DIVISION OF REAL ESTATE #100012784
THE MORTGAGEMINT, LLC, NMLS# 373773 | Originator: LANDON FARLEY, NMLS# 228663
MORTGAGEMINT®, LLC, NMLS# 373773 - Landon Farley - NMLS #228663
8310 S VALLEY HWY, THIRD FLOOR ENGLEWOOD, CO 80112
REGULATED BY THE DIVISION OF REAL ESTATE #100012784
2018 MortgageMint®, LLC
Need a Loan? … Go to The Mint!
_
